Guide to the Alfred Corn Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- September 1996 Acquisition, undated; 2; 9; (9 boxes)
  Arranged into five groupings: Letters, Incoming; Writings; Outgoing Correspondence (Unsorted); Printed Material; and Incoming Correspondence (Unsorted).
  This portion of the collection includes correspondence, writings, printed material, tapes, photographs and personal papers by or relating to Alfred Corn. Includes letters from John and Denise Carmody, Irving Feldman, Thom Gunn, Anthony Hecht, Eric Pankey, Grace Schulman, Richard Wilbur and others; writings including Autobiography and A Manual of Prosody, by Alfred Corn; and personal papers, including engagement calendars.
  Former call number: Uncat ZA MS 498
  - Letters, Incoming
    Arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
    - Baker, David (Box 18)
    - Bawer, Bruce (Box 18)
    - Belieu, Erin (Box 18)
    - Bergman, David (Box 18)
    - Bodo, Murray (Box 18)
    - Bogen, Don (Box 18)
    - Boyers, Robert (Box 18)
    - Brock-Broido, Lucie (Box 18)
    - Brown, Walter (Box 18)
    - Carmody, John and Denise (Box 18)
    - Cherry, Kelly (Box 18)
    - Christopher, Nicholas (Box 18)
    - Citino, David (Box 18)
    - Clampitt, Amy (Box 18)
    - Clifton, Lucille (Box 18)
    - Cofer, Judith Ortiz (Box 18)
    - Cole, Henri (Box 18)
    - Cummins, Jim (Box 18)
    - Doty, Mark (Box 18)
    - Dove, Rita (Box 18)
    - Eugenides, Jeffrey (Box 18)
    - Fagan, Kathy (Box 18)
    - Feldman, Irving (Box 18)
    - Ford, Harry (Box 18)
    - Gass, William (Box 18)
    - Gates, Henry Louis, Jr. (Box 18)
    - Gioia, Dana (Box 18)
    - Goldbarth, Albert (Box 18)
    - Gregor, Debora (Box 18)
    - Gunn, Thom (Box 18)
    - Hacker, Marilyn (Box 18)
    - Hadas, Rachel (Box 18)
    - Halpern, Daniel (Box 18)
    - Hamby, Barbara (Box 18)
    - Hammer, Langdon (Box 18)
    - Harnett, Gerald (Box 18)
    - Hawkins, Peter (Box 18)
    - Heaney, Seamus (Box 18)
    - Hecht, Anthony (Box 18)
    - Hill, Kathleen (Box 18)
    - Hooten, Peter (Box 18)
    - Horowitz, Roger (Box 18)
    - Howard, Richard (Box 18)
    - Howes, Barbara (Box 18)
    - Hudgins, Andrew (Box 18)
    - Jones, Ann (Box 18)
    - Karlinsky, Simon (Box 18)
    - Kirby, David (Box 18)
    - Koestenbaum, Wayne (Box 18)
    - Koethe, John (Box 18)
    - Korie, Michael (Box 18)
    - Leibowitz, Herb (Box 18)
    - Lehman, David (Box 18)
    - Leithauser, Brad (Box 18)
    - Lesser, Rika (Box 18)
    - Lesser, Wendy (Box 18)
    - Lewis, Gwynnethe (Box 18)
    - Logan, William (Box 18)
    - Longenbach, James (Box 18)
    - Lux, Thomas (Box 18)
    - McClatchy, J. D. (Box 18)
    - McCourt, James (Box 18)
    - McKenna, Rollie (Box 18)
    - Madoff, Steven H. (Box 18)
    - Malti-Douglas, Fedwa (Box 18)
    - Malmstad, John (Box 18)
    - Manrique, Jaime (Box 18)
    - Martin, Robert K. (Box 18)
    - Maso, Carol (Box 18)
    - Matthews, William (Box 18)
    - McPherson, Sandra (Box 18)
    - McPhillips, Robert (Box 18)
    - Mendelson, Edward (Box 18)
    - Merrill, James (Box 18)
    - Merrin, Judith (Box 18)
    - Mojtabai, Grace (Box 18)
    - Moore, Honor (Box 18)
    - Muski-Dukes, Carol (Box 18)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol (Box 18)
    - O'Driscoll, Dennis (Box 18)
    - Pankey, Eric (Box 18)
    - Park, Darragh (Box 18)
    - Pashen, Elise (Box 18)
    - Perloff, Marjorie (Box 18)
    - Pettingell, Phoebe (Box 19)
    - Pinsky, Robert (Box 19)
    - Phillips, Carl (Box 19)
    - Plante, David (Box 19)
    - Quinn, Alice (Box 19)
    - Rankine, Claudia (Box 19)
    - Richman, Robert (Box 19)
    - Rosenberg, David (Box 19)
    - Salter, Mary Jo (Box 19)
    - Sandy, Stephen (Box 19)
    - Schnackenberg, Gjertrud (Box 19)
    - Schillman, Grace (Box 19)
    - Selman, Robyn (Box 19)
    - Sifton, Elizabeth (Box 19)
    - Shaw, Robert B. (Box 19)
    - Slavitt, David (Box 19)
    - Strana, Mark (Box 19)
    - Temkina, Marina (Box 19)
    - Ulacia, Manuel (Box 19)
    - Vendler, Helen (Box 19)
    - Warren, Rosanna (Box 19)
    - Warner, Marina (Box 19)
    - White, Ed (Box 19)
    - Wilbur, Richard (Box 19)
    - Wojahn, David (Box 19)
    - Zinnes, Harriet (Box 19)
    - General Unsorted Correspondence (Box 19)
  - Writings
    Arranged alphabetically by author.
    - Bodo, Murray: The Earth Moves at Midnight (Box 20)
    - Bogen, Dan: The Known World (Box 20)
    - Corn, Alfred
      - Autobiographies (Box 20)
      - A Manual of Prosody (Box 20)
      - Musical Sacrifice (Box 20)
      - Part of His Story (Box 20)
      - Present (Box 20)
      - Drafts '94 (Box 20)
      - Drafts '93 (Box 20)
      - Drafts '95 (Box 20)
    - Davidoff, Sally: The Way You Look Tonight (Box 20)
    - Hightower, Scott: Sacred Borders (Box 20)
    - Long, Robert: Spanish Key (Box 20)
    - Longenbach, James: Richard Wilbur's Small World (Box 20)
    - Madoff, Steven: While You Were Here (Box 20)
    - Miller, D. A.: Place for Us (Box 20)
    - Pankey, Eric: This Reliquary World (Box 20)
    - Schulman, Grace: For That Day Only (Box 20)
    - Schultz, Susan: The Philosopher's Child (Box 20)
    - Skofield, James: Night Passage (Box 20)
    - Vojklis, John: Thesis (Box 20)
    - Zinnes, Harriet: My Haven't the Flowers Been? (Box 20)
  - Outgoing Correspondence
    Related Archival Materials note
    See also Unsorted Correspondence.
    - Unsorted letters (Box 21)
  - Printed Material
    - Article by Corn in The New York Times Book Review (Box 22)
    - Poem by Corn in Poetry Ireland Review (Box 22)
    - The Hudson Review (Box 22)
    - Poem by Corn in Partisan Review (Box 22)
    - Poems by Corn in The New Republic (Box 22)
    - Articles by Corn in The Nation (Box 22)
    - The Harvard Gay and Lesbian Review (Box 22)
    - The Nation (Box 22)
    - Article by Corn in The New York Review of Art (Box 22)
    - Article by Corn in The Threepenny Review (Box 22)
    - Theology Today (Box 22)
    - Verse (Box 22)
    - Poem by Corn in The Best Verse (Box 22)
    - Poem by Corn in the Raritan (Box 22)
    - Poem by Corn in the Anglican Theological Review (Box 22)
    - Painting in Poetry Poetry in Painting (Box 22)
    - Articles by Corn in The Kenyon Review (Box 22)
    - The Paris Review (Box 22)
    - Article by Corn in AGNI (Box 22)
    - Poem by Corn in the Princeton University (Box 22)
    - Library Chronicle (Box 22)
    - Poem by Corn in Modern Russian Literature and Culture (Box 22)
    - Article by Corn in Touchstone (Box 22)
    - ARTnews (Box 22)
    - Conference Programs (Box 23)
    - Speaking Engagements (Box 23)
    - Awards (Box 23)
    - Calendars (Box 23)
    - Kayebill (CUNY) (Box 24)
    - Manoa (Box 24)
    - ARTnews (Box 24)
    - Antaeus on Music (Box 24)
    - The New Republic (Box 24)
    - The New York Times Book Review (Box 24)
    - The Nation (Box 24)
    - Western Humanities Review (Box 24)
    - Columbia (Box 24)
    - AGNI (Box 24)
    - The Kenyon Review (Box 24)
    - Salmagundi (Box 24)
    - Park, Younh-Ha (Box 24)
    - Rosseau, Ann Marie (Box 24)
    - Toward Visual Discovery (Box 24)
    - Where Dreams Cross (Box 24)
    - Introduction for Philip Levine and Gerald Stern (Box 24)
    - Introduction for evening of George Herbert's Poetry (Box 24)
    - Poet's Notebook (Box 24)
    - FYI (Box 24)
    - LGNY (Box 24)
    - Boston Review (Box 24)
    - The Catholic World (Box 24)
    - Poetry Society of America (Box 24)
  - Outgoing Correspondence
    See also Unsorted letters.
    - Unsorted Correspondence (Box 25)
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - Unsorted Correspondence (Box 26)
- April 1999 Acquisition, 1996-1998, undated; 3; 11.25; (9 boxes)
  Purchased from Alfred Corn on the Sinclair Lewis Fund, 1999.
  Not arranged in any particular order.
  This portion of the collection includes correspondence, writings, printed material, and personal papers, including photographs. Includes Frogs, by Alfred Corn, typescript, and correspondence with Mary Jo Bang, Christopher Corwin, Kirk Read, Grace Schulman, and others.
  Former call number: Uncat ZA MS 615
  - A Ghost in the Forest by David Plante, typescript (Box 27)
  - Correspondence, 17 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence, 9 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence, 26 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence, 18 (Box 30)
    Includes correspondence with Christopher Corwin, Marilyn Hacker, Mary Jo Salter, Lynn Freed, Brad Leithauser, Grace Schulman, and others
  - Correspondence, 31 (Box 31)
    Includes correspondence with Jane Bain, Lera Chitwood, Mary Jo Salter, Susan Schultz, and others
  - Engagement calendars, 1996-1998; 2 (Box 32)
  - Printed ephemera, 5 (Box 32)
  - Writings of others, 5 (Box 32)
  - Michael Feinberg's translation of Thomas Bernhard's Heldenplatz (Box 32)
  - A Kiss in Space by Mary Jo Salter (Box 32)
  - Aeolian Kazoo by Downing (Box 32)
  - Night Life by Paul Schmidt (Box 32)
  - Harlequin Romance by Nola Tully (Box 32)
  - Shift by Jeredith Merrin (Box 32)
  - North Star by Louis S. Asekoff (Box 32)
  - Infidelities by Elise Paschen (Box 32)
  - Driving the Living by Tracy K. Smith (Box 32)
  - Sapphics by Grace Schulman (Box 32)
  - Shared Pillow by Scott Hightower (Box 32)
  - Broken Symmetry by David Citino (Box 32)
  - Aleatory Allegories by Susan Schultz (Box 32)
  - Poems by Eric Pankey (Box 32)
  - True North by Stephanie Strickland (Box 32)
  - Printed material, 16 (Box 33)
  - Frogs translated by Alfred Corn, 3 (Box 34)
  - Autobiographies by Alfred Corn (Box 34)
  - Stake: Poems, 1972-1992 by Alfred Corn (Box 34)
  - Jaffa and The Unknown Poets by Alfred Corn, printed version, New England Review (Box 34)
  - Pith Helmets by Alfred Corn, printed version, The Georgia Review (Box 34)
  - Present by Alfred Corn, 3 (Box 34)
  - Part of His Story by Alfred Corn (Box 34)
  - Writings by Kenward Elmslie (Box 34)
  - Writings by David Mason (Box 34)
  - Terror: A Novel by David Plante (Box 34)
  - A Manual of Prosody by Alfred Corn (Box 34)
  - Miranda's Book by Alfred Corn (Box 34)
  - Review of Alfred Corn's The Poem's Heartbeat by David Kirby (Box 34)
  - Poetry by Jane Bain (Box 34)
  - Alfred Corn's passport and photographs (Box 34)
  - Printed material, 13 (Box 35)
  - Drafts of poems by Alfred Corn, typescripts, corrected, 2 (Box 35)
- April 1999 Acquisition, undated; 4; 0.21; (1 box)
  This portion of the collection includes printed material, including magazines and newspapers; and correspondence to Alfred Corn from Columbia University. This material was transferred from the Printed Acquisitions unit of the Beinecke Library.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 84
  - Printed material, 7 (Box 36)
  - Correspondence to Alfred Corn from Columbia University (Box 36)
- November 2003 Acquisition, 1968-1989; 5; 1.25; (1 box)
  Purchased from Alfred Corn on the Sinclair Lewis Fund, 2003.
  This portion of the collection includes ten journals.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 434
  - Journals, 1968 January - 1989 October; 10 (Box 37)
- September 2004 Acquisition, 1969-2001; 6; 5.08; (6 boxes)
  Purchased from Alfred Corn on the Eugene G. O'Neill Memorial Fund, 2004.
  Arranged into four groupings: Correspondence, Writings, Other Papers, and Audiovisual Material.
  This portion of the collection includes correspondence, writings, photographs, printed material, video cassettes and other papers by or relating to Alfred Corn.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 713
  - Correspondence
    - E-mail correspondence, 9 (Box 38)
    - E-mail correspondence, 4 (Box 38)
    - E-mail correspondence, 9 (Box 39)
    - E-mail correspondence, 5 (Box 39)
    - Outgoing correspondence, 4 (Box 40)
    - Incoming correspondence, 5 (Box 40)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 7 (Box 40)
  - Writings
    - Works by Corn
      - Miranda's book (Box 41)
      - Contradictions (Box 41)
      - MS of Contradictions (Box 41)
      - Drafts, 4 (Box 41)
      - Misc. Poems (Box 41)
    - Works by Others
      - Boland, Evan, "Moving Statues" (Box 41)
      - Cash, Arthur, "A Meditation Upon Death" (Box 41)
      - Fragos, Emily, "Little Savage" (Box 41)
      - Foy, John, "Techne's Cleaning House" (Box 41)
      - Holland, Walter, "The Calamus Root: American Gay Poetry Since World War II" (Box 41)
      - LB (Editor), "Intermediating Surfaces: The Sk(In) Between" (Box 41)
      - Manrique, Jaime, "Senoritas in Love: a tragicomedy" (Box 41)
      - Mason, David, "Arrivals" (Box 41)
      - Mathews, Richard, "The Mill is Burning" (Box 41)
      - Mojtabai, AG, "All the Road Ging" (Box 41)
      - Roush, Jason, "Breezeways" (Box 41)
      - Roush, Jason, "After Hours" (Box 41)
      - Schneebaum, Tobias, "The Circus" and "The Mysterious East" (Box 41)
      - Zuba, Jesse, "Alfred Corn Interviews" (Box 41)
  - Other papers
    - Electronic Files (Box 42)
      Original computer disks are restricted. Copies of electronic files are available through Access Services.
      Available through Access Services:
      2004-ycal-0923-a-0001: "An Interview with Alfred Corn (diskette mailed to AC for editing)" - [3.5].
    - Biographical material, 3 (Box 42)
    - Passport, identification cards (Box 42)
    - Journal, 1969-1974 (Box 42)
    - Calendar, 2001 (Box 42)
    - Calendar, 2002 (Box 42)
    - Calendar, 2003 (Box 42)
    - Photographs (Box 42)
    - The New York Review of Books, 2001 July 29 (Box 42)
    - The New Yorker, 2000 March 13 (Box 42)
    - Clippings, reviews (Box 42)
    - Announcements, fliers, programs, awards, brochures, 8 (Box 42)
    - Poster for Athens Literary Festival (Box 43)
  - Audiovisual material
    - Alfred Corn and Teresa Miller "WRITING OUT LOUD 2/4/02", 2002 February 2; YCALMSS605_0003; 1; 00:40:59 (Box 43, Item barcode 39002102338937)
    - Saad and Mess Entertainment "Gotham TV Episode #g 10 11/27/2000", 2000 November 27; YCALMSS605_0004; 1; 00:59:59 (Box 43, Item barcode 39002102338945)
    - AC reading novel, 1; 01:33:57; The program is in silence from approximately 01:08:49 until 01:21:52 on the tape. (Box 43, Item barcode 39002099362247)
    - AC reading poems, Djerassi Foundation, 1988 May 10; 1; 01:17:57; The program is in silence from approximately 01:08:38 until 01:12:45 on the tape. (Box 43, Item barcode 39002099362239)
      A list of contents is included.
      Side A / Side B
      "Promised Land Valley, June '73"
      "Chinese Porcelains at the Metropolitan"
      "To a Muse"
      "Toward Skellig Michael"
      "Navidad, St. Nicholas Ave."
      "New Year"
      "An Xmas Murder"
      "At the Grave of Wallace Stevens"
      "The Village"
      Part One: sections I-III ("From Notes From a Child of Paradise")
      Part Three: sections XVI and XX ("From Notes From a Child of Paradise")
      "Lost and Found"
      "Naskeag"
      "Wild Carrot"
      "Assistances"
      "Welcome to Farewell" from "After Ireland", "Dublin: The Liberties"
  - Computer media
    Restricted fragile material. Reference copies of electronic files are available. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - An Interview With Alfred Corn (diskette mailed to AC For editing), 2004-ycal-0923-a-0001; 1 (Box 43A)
      Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
- September 2004 Acquisition, undated; 7; 0.83; (2 boxes)
  This portion of the collection includes correspondence (electronic mail printouts) between Alfred Corn and others, including Mary Jo Salter, Henri Cole and others.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 738
  - Outgoing correspondence, 13 (Box 44)
  - Incoming and outgoing correspondence, 12 (Box 45)
- September 2004 Acquisition, undated; 8; 0.42; (1 box)
  This portion of the collection consists of printed material, including Art in America and Black book. This material was originally transferred to the Printed Acquisitions unit of the Beinecke Library, but was subsequently returned to the collection.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 783
  - Printed material, 10 (Box 46)
- October 2007 Acquisition, 1994-2007; 9; 2; (2 boxes)
  Purchased from Glenn Horowitz Bookseller on the Carl Van Vechten Fund, 2007.
  This portion of the collection consists of writings, correspondence, photographs, printed material, video cassettes, and other papers.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 979
  - Writings by Corn
    - Blue Roses, 2004 (Box 47)
    - Lady Day (Box 47)
    - Miranda's Book (Box 47)
    - Poems, 4 (Box 47)
    - Poems, 2003-2007 (Box 47)
  - Travel Diaries, 1994-1997; 2 (Box 47)
  - Writings by Others, Typescripts
    - Green, Yvonne; Identities (Box 47)
    - Howard, Richard; To Constantine Cavafy (Box 47)
    - Pinksy, Robert; Life of David (Box 47)
    - Pousson, Martin; Sugar (Box 47)
    - Richie, Eugene; Poems (Box 47)
    - Roush, Jason; Crosstown (Box 47)
    - Schulman, Grace; Broken String (Box 47)
    - Scott, Benjamin; Auctioneer Bangs His Gavel (Box 47)
    - Shankar, Ravi; Waze-Ray-Earth (Box 47)
    - Poems by Others (Box 47)
  - Correspondence, 11 (Box 47)
  - E-Mail printouts, 2004-2007; 13 (Box 48)
  - Date book 2004, 2004-2006; 3 (Box 48)
  - Photographs, 5 (Box 48)
  - [My Neighborhood], undated; YCALMSS605_0001; 1; 00:28:25 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002102301810)
  - Dracula by David Del Tredici, text by Alfred Corn, undated; YCALMSS605_0002; 1; 00:27:18 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002102301828)
  - Invitations (Box 48)
  - Name Tag (Box 48)
  - Programs (Box 48)
  - Printed material, 2 (Box 48)
- November 2010 Acquisition, 1948-2010; Series X; 1.63; (4 boxes)
  Purchased from Glenn Horowitz Bookseller on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund, 2010.
  Contains correspondence, drafts of writings, and photographs.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 1251
  - Correspondence [e-mails], 2006-2007 (Box 49)
  - Correspondence, 2007-2009; 2 (Box 49)
  - Correspondence, 2007-2010; 4 (Box 49)
  - Correspondence, 2008-2009; 5 (Box 49)
  - Corn, Alfred - Balance (Box 49)
  - Corn, Alfred - Diary, 2007 (Box 49)
  - Corn, Alfred - Erin Belieu - Reading, Fordham University, 1996 February 26 (Box 49)
  - Corn, Alfred - Introduction to Talk on Grace Schulman, 2007 April 14 (Box 49)
  - Corn, Alfred - Michaux and the Organic, undated (Box 49)
  - Corn, Alfred - Modern Sequence in Prose about the Modern Poetic Sequence, undated (Box 49)
  - Corn, Alfred - Notebook, undated (Box 49)
  - Corn, Alfred - Poetry - drafts, undated; 2 (Box 49)
  - Corn, Alfred - Reader's report for Karl Kirchwey, Poems under Saturn..., 2007 April 14 (Box 49)
  - Corn, Alfred - Tables, undated; 2 (Box 49)
  - Corn, Alfred - Thompson Gunn reading - introduction, undated (Box 49)
  - Corn, Alfred - Untitled work, 2010 Summer (Box 49)
  - Corn, Alfred - Untitled work, undated (Box 49)
  - Battle, Laura - Untitled Works, undated (Box 49)
  - Byrne, Edward - Seeded Light, 2009 (Box 49)
  - Connarroe, Joel - More Leaves from a Lucky Life, 2008 Autumn (Box 49)
  - Finch, Annie - American Witch, 2009 February 5 (Box 49)
  - Fox, John - Book of Common Tasks, 2007 (Box 49)
  - Hill, Kathleen - Who Occupies this House?, 2010 (Box 49)
  - Khalvati, Mimi - Poems, 2009 February 7 (Box 49)
  - Livingston, Chip - Museum of False Starts, undated (Box 50)
  - Locke, Christopher - End of American Magic, undated (Box 50)
  - Shapiro, David - Collages, undated (Box 50)
  - Del Tredici, David - Untitled Sheet Music, 1996 August 30 (Box 50)
  - Vogelsang, Arthur - Poems, 2010 (Box 50)
  - Vogelsang, Arthur - [Vogelsang - Expedition], 2010 (Box 50)
  - Calendar, 2010 (Box 50)
  - Date book, 2007 (Box 50)
  - Date book, 2008 (Box 50)
  - Personal Papers, circa 2008 (Box 50)
  - Photographs, 1948-1953; 3 (Box 50)
  - Crampton, Nancy - Photographs, undated (Box 51)
  - Photographs, undated; 2 (Box 51)
  - Photographs, circa 2008 (Box 51)
  - Printed Material, circa 2008 (Box 51)
  - Readings, 2008-2009 (Box 51)
  - Terraces of Relleu, 2008 (Box 51)
  - Travel related papers, 2008 (Box 51)
  - Wolf - Poster - N.Y., 2000s (Box 51)
  - Electronic Files (Box 51)
    Existence and Location of Copies
    2010-ycal-40674-0001: "Untitled disk" - [3.5].
    2010-ycal-40674-0002: "Corn 7/29/1999" - [3.5].
    2010-ycal-40674-0003: "[Brown], Walter - Photographs" - [CD].
  - Miscellaneous printed ephemera removed from printed material, 1983 (Box 51)
  - A new life, typescript, signed and proof; A walk in Hart Crane's village, program (Box 51)
  - Computer media
    - [no label information], 2010-ycal-40674-0001; 1 (Box 52)
    - 1 Corn 7/29/99, 2010-ycal-40674-0002; 1 (Box 52)
    - [no label information], 2010-ycal-40674-0003; 1 (Box 52)
    - [no label information], 2010-ycal-40674-0004; 1 (Box 52)
- August 2011 Acquisition, 1984-1990; Series XI; 0.21; (1 box)
  Purchased from Glenn Horowitz Bookseller on the George B. Alvord Fund, 2011.
  Contains correspondence and printed material.
  - Correspondence to Ted Danforth and Jimmy Frederickson with related printed material, 1984-1990 (Box 53)
- January 2012 Acquisition, 1989-1999; Series XII; 0.83; (2 boxes)
  Purchased from Glenn Horowitz Bookseller on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund, 2012.
  Contains journals.
  - Journals, 1989-1999; 5 (Box 54)
  - Journals, 1989-1999; 4 (Box 55)